blogandwatch.me 2012-06-11

# Blog and Watch ME - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

The privacy of our members is our top priority. Please read this page to learn about our privacy policy.

### What this Privacy Policy covers

This policy covers how BlogAndWatch.ME ("B&W", "we", "us", "our") treats the personal information that B&W collects and receives from its website visitors and members ("you", "your"). This policy covers the website http://BlogAndWatch.ME and all pages on its domain name. When you click a link or otherwise leave this domain name, our privacy policy will no longer apply. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that B&W does not own or control, or to people that B&W does not employ or manage.

### General

B&W collects and stores your personal information when you visit our website, create an account, login, make a purchase, or contact our support team for help. We automatically receive and record your personal information on our servers from your web browser, including your IP address, cookies set by B&W, and the page you request.

We use this information to analyze and improve our website and business and provide a better user experience.

We do not rent, sell or share your personal information with any third parties. The only persons with access to your personal information are high-level B&W employees on a "need-to-know" basis.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order of legal process served on us. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms and Conditions, or as otherwise required by law.

In the event B&W is acquired or merges with another entity, B&W may transfer your personal information to the new entity.

You agree that: These Terms of Use, together with the Privacy Notice at http://www.BlogAndWatch.ME and any other legal notices published by B&W on its website, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and B&W concerning the B&W online services. If any provision of these Terms of Use is deemed invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term of these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term of any other term, and B&W's failure to assert any right or provision under these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. B&W reserves the right to amend these Terms of Use at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review these Terms of Use for any changes. Your use of the B&W services following any amendment of these Terms of Use will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. YOU AND B&W AGREE THAT ANY CAUSE OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE B&W ONLINE SERVICES MUST COMMENCE WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCURES. OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION IS PERMANENTLY BARRED.

### Your e-mail address

Your e-mail address is used to contact you on a transactional basis. For example, we will send you an e-mail when you sign up for your membership, make a purchase, request a lost password, and so forth.

Your e-mail address may be used to send you our newsletter featuring website updates, which is sent very rarely, no more than a few times per year.

### Your payment information

B&W itself does not process credit cards, and B&W does not collect or store credit card information. We rely on trusted third-party payment processors, providers, and gateways to process transactions for our website. We do not have access to your credit card information.

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies may record information a user accesses on one webpage to simplify subsequent interactions with that website by the same user, or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related web pages. Cookies make it easier for a user to move from webpage to webpage and to complete transactions over the Internet. You may learn more about cookies at the following URL: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie

Most major web browsers are set up so that they will initially accept cookies, but you may modify your computer's preferences to issue you an alert when a cookie is downloaded, or to disable the ability of third parties to download a cookie to you.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but you may have to re-enter your username and password more often and you may experience some other unexpected browsing inconveniences.

Other companies do not have access to cookies set by B&W.

Your ability to access, edit and delete your Personal Information

For privacy and security reasons, we do not provide online access for members to their personal information.

You may request that we delete your Personal Information by contacting our Support team.

Despite the foregoing and even though you have requested us to remove information, we will retain in our files certain data such as information used to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, comply with credit card merchant banking and association agreements, enhance security, reduce fraud, comply with Federal and State law, or to enforce any agreements, policies, and rules governing your use of our website. Removed information also may persist in backup copies and/or other users' cashes.

If you have any further questions about your Personal Information, please [Contact Us](http://blogandwatch.me/index.php/Contact/Blog-And-Watch-ME-Support-Team.html).

### Confidentiality and security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We limit access to your personal information and e-mail address to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information.

### Minors

B&W is an adult site and access to persons under the age of 18 is strictly prohibited. We have no intention of collecting any personal information from individuals under eighteen years of age. If a minor has provided us with personal information, a parent or guardian of that minor should Contact Support and we will remove this information from our existing files.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy or e-mail practices

B&W reserves its right, at its sole and absolute discretion, to revise, amend, modify or revoke this Privacy Policy at any time and in any manner to the fullest extent permitted by law. Changes to this Policy will be effective by posting revisions on the Privacy Policy link on the B&W website.

If we make changes in our e-mail practices or in the way we use your e-mail address, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy.

### Contact Information

If you have questions or suggestions, please [Contact us](http://blogandwatch.me/index.php/Contact/Blog-And-Watch-ME-Support-Team.html)
